http://www.turningturnip.co.uk/privacy/

Privacy PolicyHomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyNOTICE: www.turningturnip.co.uk is owned and operated by Short Fuse Creative Ltd.At Short Fuse Creative Ltd, we are dedicated to preserving the confidence and trust of visitors to www.turningturnip.co.uk and all of our other websites. We want you to be assured that Short Fuse Creative Ltd does not trade, sell or rent email lists with other businesses or individuals for marketing purposes. We will never do this. This privacy Policy will cover this in full, so that you can be confident that Short Fuse Creative Ltd will protect your Privacy rights under law.Personal identification informationWe may collect some of your personal identification information. This may happen whenever you:Visiting our www.turningturnip.co.ukWhen filling in the contact page formYou may be asked for your name, email address and other personal details. However, you may also visit our website anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us for advertising your business information or other purposes. You can always refuse to supply personally identification information. However, this may prevent you from engaging in certain activities on our website.Non-personal identification informationWe may collect non-personal identification information about you whenever you visit our website. This may include:Browser typeType of computerScreen resolutionYour operating systemInternet service providerWeb browser cookiesOur website uses cookies to enhance your experience. Your web browser saves cookies on your hard drive. This is for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track limited information about you. You may choose to set your web browser to block cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do block cookies, some parts of our website may not work properly. The reason why we collect cookies is because we use a third party service – Google Analytics to track user interaction with the website. We make no attempt to collect the identities of our visitors.How we use collected informationShort Fuse Creative Ltd may collect and use your personal information for the following purposes:To improve customer service: The information you provide us with, helps us respond to your needs more efficiently.To personalize your experience: We may use visitor information to help us understand how our users as a group use the services and resources on our website.To improve our website: We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.To send occasional emails: If you have given consent, we may use your email address to send you information and updates. It’s information may also be used to respond to your inquiries, questions, and other requests. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing lists, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or by emailing our data protection officer James Middleton – info@turningturnip.co.uk.How we protect your informationWe adopt appropriate security measures to protect our website and database from hackers. These measures protect your personal information stored on our website against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction.Sharing your personal informationWe do not sell, trade, or rent your personal identification information to others. We may share generic, non-personal demographic information regarding our visitors with trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.Third party websitesWe allow for other forms of advertising on our website. Third party pay-per-click and affiliate advertising is used to help fund our website so we can continue to offer free advertising to dance related businesses and groups. We can’t always control the content of these third party adverts. Although we are not responsible for the practices used by our advertisers, we do take every measure possible to avoid causing offence or conflict. These companies may have their own privacy polices and terms.AdvertisingThird-party adverts appearing on our website may use cookies. These cookies allow the advertisers to recognize your computer to tailor an advertisement. These are delivered using non-personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third-party advertisers.Google AdsenseMost of our third-party advertising is from Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie which enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to our website and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non-personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at https://policies.google.com/technologies/adsAccess to your personal informationIf you wish to be removed from our mailing lists, contact our data protection officer James Middleton – info@turningturnip.co.uk.Changes to this privacy policyShort Fuse Creative Ltd has the right to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our website. We encourage you to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.Your acceptance of these termsBy using this website, you signify your acceptance of this privacy policy. If you don’t agree to this privacy policy, then please don’t use our website. Your continued use of this website, following the posting of changes to this privacy policy will be viewed as your acceptance of those changes.Contacting usIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:Short Fuse Creative Ltd – https://www.shortfusecreative.co.uk5 Stockton Hill, Dawlish, Devon EX7 9LZ United KingdomCompany Number: 797107601626 863367 – info@shortfusecreative.co.ukThis document was last updated on April 27, 2018ShareTweetSearch Search for:
ServicesAdobe Photoshop Specialist: Photo Editing & Photo RetouchingPhoto Retouching Services UKPhoto-Retouching – Price GeneratorProfessional Photo Manipulation ServicesProfessional Image Clipping Path ServicesAdobe Photoshop Consultant – James MiddletonPhotoshop Project WorkContactCall for our Adobe Photoshop UK photo retouching services: 01626 863367Search Search for:
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Privacy & Cookies Policy
Close Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessaryAny cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website. HomeServicesPhoto RetouchingImage ManipulationPrice GuideClipping Path ServicesImage ConsultationAdobe Photoshop SpecialistExamplesPhoto RetouchingAdvanced Photo EditingFreebiesPhotoshop ActionsPhotoshop Video TutorialsMySQL & PHP GeneratorWordPress Customise GeneratorEmail Form GeneratorContact
